Guide to the Records of the Asian/Pacific/American Institute RG.21.35
New York University Archives
- Series VI: Media, 182066
  - DVCs, 182748
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel 2, 2002 October 11; RG2135_50; 182995 (Box 20)
    - G. Okihiro Brown Bag, 2003 April 24; RG2135_51; 182996 (Box 20)
    - G. Okihiro Brown Bag, 2003 April 24; RG2135_52; 182997 (Box 20)
    - Greg Robinson, 2002 March 28; RG2135_53; 182998 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Daughters of Taiwan, RG2135_54; 182999 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--When You Look At Me What Do You See?, RG2135_55; 183000 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Navigating the Next Wave, RG2135_56; 183001 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Parachutes Across the Country, RG2135_57; 183002 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Juxtapositions Queer Politics, RG2135_58; 183003 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--International, Regional, and Local Networks, RG2135_59; 183004 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Kazakhstan Adventures, RG2135_60; 183005 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Welcome, RG2135_61; 183006 (Box 20)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination--Travelers a Month in NYC, RG2135_62; 183007 (Box 20)
    - Jessica Hagedorn Dogeaters Panel, 2001 January 30; RG2135_63; 183008 (Box 20)
    - Jessica Hagedorn Dogeaters Panel, 2001 January 30; RG2135_64; 183009 (Box 20)
    - Kieng Sen Ong Meet the Artist, 2002 February 7; RG2135_65; 183010 (Box 20)
    - Maya Lin and Michael Brenson Dialogue, RG2135_66; 183011 (Box 20)
    - Maya Lin and Michael Brenson Dialogue, RG2135_67; 183012 (Box 20)
    - Pacific Islands, Atlantic Worlds--Anthropological Engagement, 2001 October 26; RG2135_68; 183013 (Box 20)
    - Pacific Islands, Atlantic Worlds--Anthropological Engagement, 2001 October 26; RG2135_69; 183014 (Box 20)
    - Pacific Islands, Atlantic Worlds, 2001 October 26; RG2135_70; 183015 (Box 20)
    - Pacific Islands, Atlantic Worlds-US Continental Pacific Islander Diaspora, 2001 October 26; RG2135_71; 183016 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Opening Night and Southeast Asian Food Panel, 2001 April 19; RG2135_72; 183017 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Cultural Presentation, 2001 April 19; RG2135_73; 183018 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Cooking Demonstration and Discussion, 2001 April 20; RG2135_74; 183019 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Cooking Demonstration and Discussion, 2001 April 20; RG2135_75; 183020 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--NYC Appetites, 2001 April 20; RG2135_76; 183021 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--NYC Appetites and Food Travels, 2001 April 20; RG2135_77; 183022 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Food Travels, 2001 April 20; RG2135_78; 183023 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Slideshow, Lecture, and Tastings, 2001 April 20; RG2135_79; 183024 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Slideshow, Lecture, and Tastings, 2001 April 20; RG2135_80; 183025 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Southeast Asian Curries, 2001 April 20; RG2135_81; 183026 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Southeast Asian Curries, 2001 April 20; RG2135_82; 183027 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Cooking Demonstration, 2001 April 21; RG2135_83; 183028 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Cooking Demonstration, 2001 April 21; RG2135_84; 183029 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Cooking Demonstration, 2001 April 21; RG2135_85; 183030 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Roundtable Healing and Nutritional Values, 2001 April 21; RG2135_86; 183031 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Roundtable Healing and Nutritional Values, 2001 April 21; RG2135_87; 183032 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Roundtable on Religious Ideologies, 2001 April 21; RG2135_88; 183033 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Roundtable on Religious Ideologies, 2001 April 21; RG2135_89; 183034 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Slideshow/Lecture/Tastings, 2001 April 21; RG2135_90; 183035 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Slideshow/Lecture/Tastings, 2001 April 21; RG2135_91; 183036 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Southeast Asian Crossroads, 2001 April 21; RG2135_92; 183037 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Southeast Asian Crossroads, 2001 April 21; RG2135_93; 183038 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--US Media and Southeast Asian Cuisine, 2001 April 21; RG2135_94; 183039 (Box 20)
    - Palates of Pleasure--US Media and Southeast Asian Cuisine, 2001 April 21; RG2135_95; 183040 (Box 20)
    - PDA Opening, 1998 November 12; RG2135_96; 183041 (Box 20)
    - PDA Opening, 1998 November 12; RG2135_97; 183042 (Box 20)
    - PDA After Party, 1998 November 14; RG2135_98; 183043 (Box 20)
    - Rethinking NYC, 2002 October 30; RG2135_99; 183044 (Box 20)
    - Rethinking NYC, 2002 October 19; RG2135_100; 183045 (Box 20)
    - Rethinking NYC, 2002 October 30; RG2135_101; 183046 (Box 20)
    - Social Work Conference--Opening Remarks, 2000 March 31; RG2135_102; 183047 (Box 20)
    - Social Work Conference--On Current State of Mental Health Services, RG2135_103; 183048 (Box 20)
    - Social Work Conference--On Migration and Identity, RG2135_104; 183049 (Box 20)
    - Social Work Conference--On Migration and Identity, RG2135_105; 183050 (Box 20)
    - Social Work Conference--On Cross Cultural Clinical Practice, 2000 April 1; RG2135_106; 183051 (Box 20)
    - Social Work Conference--On Match And Mismatch, RG2135_107; 183052 (Box 20)
    - Social Work Conference, RG2135_108; 183053 (Box 20)
    - Social Work Conference--On Psychoanalytic Therapy, RG2135_109; 183054 (Box 20)
    - Social Work Conference--On Psychoanalytic Therapy, RG2135_110; 183055 (Box 20)
    - Social Work Conference--On Cultural Competence Training, RG2135_111; 183056 (Box 20)
    - Suheir Hammad, 2001 February 21; RG2135_112; 183057 (Box 20)
    - Thuy Le Reading, 1999 October 28; RG2135_113; 183058 (Box 20)
    - Thuy Le Reading, 1999 October 28; RG2135_114; 183059 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--Gamalinda, RG2135_115; 183060 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--Body Count, RG2135_116; 183061 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--Body Count, RG2135_118; 183063 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--Body Count, RG2135_117; 183062 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--Looking the Other Way, RG2135_119; 183064 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--Looking the Other Way, RG2135_120; 183065 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--Looking the Other Way, RG2135_121; 183066 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--The Object of Colonial Desire, RG2135_122; 183067 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--The Object of Colonial Desire, RG2135_123; 183068 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--The Object of Colonial Desire, RG2135_124; 183069 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--Past Meets Present, RG2135_125; 183070 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--Past Meets Present, RG2135_126; 183071 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--Past Meets Present, RG2135_127; 183072 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--Reception, 1999 February 19; RG2135_128; 183073 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--Reception, 1999 February 19; RG2135_129; 183074 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--View from the Diaspora, RG2135_130; 183075 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--View from the Diaspora, RG2135_131; 183076 (Box 20)
    - Vestiges of War--View from the Diaspora, RG2135_132; 183077 (Box 20)
    - Vijay Iyer and Kuni, 2003 April 3; RG2135_133; 183078 (Box 20)
    - Vijay Iyer and Kuni, 2003 April 3; RG2135_134; 183079 (Box 20)
    - Winifred Lam Question and Answer, 2002 November 6; RG2135_135; 183080 (Box 20)
    - Winifred Lam Question and Answer, 2002 November 6; RG2135_136; 183081 (Box 20)
    - You Are Being Watched, 2003 February 7; RG2135_137; 183082 (Box 20)
    - You Are Being Watched, 2003 February 7; RG2135_138; 183083 (Box 20)
    - You Are Being Watched, 2003 February 7; RG2135_139; 183084 (Box 20)
    - Youth Forum Meetings, 1999-2000; RG2135_140; 183085 (Box 20)
    - Youth Forum Meetings, 2000; RG2135_141; 183086 (Box 20)
    - Youth Forum Meetings, 2000; RG2135_142; 183087 (Box 20)
    - Youth Forum Youth Training, 2000; RG2135_143; 183088 (Box 20)
    - Youth Identity Forum--Exploring the Unseen and Unspoken, 2000 April 7; RG2135_144; 183089 (Box 20)
    - Youth Identity Forum--Exploring the Unseen and Unspoken, 2000 April 7; RG2135_145; 183090 (Box 20)
    - Youth Identity Forum--Exploring the Unseen and Unspoken, 2000 April 7; RG2135_146; 183091 (Box 20)
    - Youth Identity Forum, 1999 March 5; RG2135_147; 184269 (Box 20)
    - Race and Social Justice: Diallo Verdict, March 2000; RG2135_148; 184279 (Box 20)
    - Race and Social Justice: Diallo Verdict, March 2000; RG2135_149; 184280 (Box 20)
    - Race and Social Justice: Diallo Verdict, March 2000; RG2135_150; 184281 (Box 20)
  - CD, 182756
    - AWU at NYU, 2004 September 25; cuid474; 182846 (Box 19)
    - Jamez, cuid475; 182847 (Box 19)
    - APAYA, 2001-2006; cuid477; 184442 (Box 19)
    - Workshops, cuid478; 184443 (Box 19)
    - APAYA Tshirt, 2005; cuid479; 184449 (Box 19)
    - APAYA Logo, 2005; cuid480; 184450 (Box 19)
    - APAYA Logo, cuid481; 184451 (Box 19)
  - VHS, 182750
    - ACEH Indonesia Conference, 1998 December 12; cuid482; 182783 (Box 18)
    - ACEH Indonesia Conference, 1998 December 12; cuid483; 182784 (Box 18)
    - ACEH Indonesia Conference, 1998 December 12; cuid484; 182785 (Box 18)
    - APAYA Trailer, cuid485; 182786 (Box 18)
    - Artist in Residence Kickoff Celebration, 2004; cuid486; 182787 (Box 18)
    - Asians in America--NYU Equal, 1996; cuid487; 182788 (Box 18)
    - Asian American Conference, 1997; cuid488; 182789 (Box 18)
    - Asian American Conference, 1997; cuid489; 182790 (Box 18)
    - Asian American Conference Phil Nash, 1997; cuid490; 182791 (Box 18)
    - Asian American Conference Phil Nash, 1997; cuid491; 182792 (Box 18)
    - Asian Women United Reunion, 2004 September 25; cuid492; 182793 (Box 18, Cassette cuid492, E-records nyuarchives_rg21.35, E-records cuid492)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Format: VHS, Duration: 84 min, Color, Sound
    - Breaking Stereotypes--APA Musicians, 2003 April 3; cuid493; 182794 (Box 18)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series with John Kuo Wei Tchen--Revisioning the City, cuid494; 182795 (Box 18)
    - Chang Rae Lee Reading, 2000 April 11; cuid495; 182796 (Box 18)
    - Civil Rights Issues and Post 9-11, 2003 May 21; cuid496; 182797 (Box 18)
    - Corky Lee Artist Talk, 2003 March 4; cuid497; 182798 (Box 18)
    - Corky Lee and Mel Rosenthal's Two Men, Two Cameras, Different Perspectives, 2002 December 5; cuid498; 182799 (Box 18)
    - Dale Minami Lecture, 2003 September 22; cuid499; 182800 (Box 18)
    - Dangerous Music, Fierce Women Reading, 1998 October 29; cuid500; 182801 (Box 18)
    - Dogeaters from Novel to Stage, 2001 January 30; cuid501; 182802 (Box 18)
    - Dogeaters from Novel to Stage, 2001 January 30; cuid502; 182803 (Box 18)
    - Emerging Artists--Stacy Ann Chin's I Was Born With Two Tongues, 1999 November 17; cuid503; 182804 (Box 18)
    - Emerging Artists--Stacy Ann Chin's I Was Born With Two Tongues, 1999 November 17; cuid504; 182805 (Box 18)
    - Fay Chiang Artist in Residence, 2003-2004; cuid505; 182806 (Box 18)
    - Flower Drum Song on NYU Tonight and CNN Student Bureau, cuid506; 182807 (Box 18)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Symposium, 2002 October 11; cuid507; 182808 (Box 18)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Annual Asian/Pacifics in America Conference, 2002 October 12; cuid508; 182809 (Box 18)
    - Flower Drum Song Camera, cuid509; 182810 (Box 18)
    - Flower Drum Song Camera, cuid510; 182811 (Box 18)
    - Jaishri Abichandani Meet the Artist, 2002 June 12; cuid511; 182812 (Box 18)
    - Maya Lin and Michael Brenson Dialogue, 1998 September 23; cuid512; 182813 (Box 18)
    - Maya Lin and Michael Brenson Dialogue, 1998 September 23; cuid513; 182814 (Box 18)
    - Nobuko in A Grain Of Sand, 1995 June 9-25; cuid514; 182815 (Box 18)
    - Rethinking NYC, 2002 October 30; cuid515; 182816 (Box 18)
    - Sia Figiel Reading, 2000 April 13; cuid516; 182817 (Box 18)
    - Third World Newsreel, cuid517; 182818 (Box 18)
    - Third World Newsreel, cuid518; 182819 (Box 18)
    - Third World Newsreel, cuid519; 182820 (Box 18)
    - Two Bells, Two Worlds Film Screening and Discussion, 2003 October 4; cuid520; 182821 (Box 18)
    - Wen Ho Lee, 2002 February 13; cuid521; 182822 (Box 18)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond, 2003 April 23; cuid522; 182823 (Box 18)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond, 2003 April 23; cuid523; 182824 (Box 18)
    - You Are Being Watched, 2003 February 7; 2018-02; cuid524; 182825 (Box 18, Cassette cuid524, E-records nyuarchives_rg21.35, E-records nyuarchives_rg21.35_cuid524, Box ACCESS 15)
      Original format: VHS, Duration: 133 min.
    - Youth Forum Training, 2000 March 25; cuid525; 182826 (Box 18)
  - DVCAM, 182751
    - Flower Drum Song--A Roundtable Discussion, 2002 October 6; cuid526; 182827 (Box 19)
    - Flower Drum Song--With C.Y. Lee Interview, 2002 October 6; cuid527; 182828 (Box 19)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond Teach In, cuid528; 182830 (Box 19)
    - Wen Ho Lee's My Country Versus Me, 2002 April 1; cuid529; 182829 (Box 19)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond Teach In, cuid530; 182831 (Box 19)
  - Floppy Disk, 182752
    - Asians in America, 1997; cuid531; 182832 (Box 19)
    - Asians in America, 1997; cuid532; 182833 (Box 19)
    - Asians in America, 1997; cuid533; 182834 (Box 19)
    - Asians in America, 1997; cuid534; 182835 (Box 19)
    - Asians in America, 1997; cuid535; 182836 (Box 19)
    - Japanese American National--Images for America's Concentration Camps, cuid536; 182837 (Box 19)
    - White House Initiative on AAPIs and FreeZone Symposium, cuid537; 184445 (Box 19)
    - APAYA, cuid538; 184452 (Box 19)
    - APAYA 01 Group Picture, Circa 2001-2002; cuid539; 221939 (Box 19)
    - APAYA 01 Nchink, Circa 2001-2002; cuid540; 221940 (Box 19)
    - Unlabeled 1 of 2, Undated; cuid541; 221941 (Box 19)
    - Unlabeled 2 of 2, Undated; cuid542; 221942 (Box 19)
  - DAT, 182753
    - Raising Our Voices, 2002 September 19; cuid543; 182838 (Box 19)
  - Hi8 ProMP, 182754
    - Asians in America--Poetics of Politics and Sex, 1999; cuid544; 182839 (Box 19)
    - Asians in America--Representant Blues, 1999; cuid545; 182840 (Box 19)
    - Asians in America--Conversations with Elaine Kim, 1999; cuid546; 182841 (Box 19)
    - Asians in America--Is The Book Dead?, 1999; cuid547; 182842 (Box 19)
    - Asians in America--Book Reading, 1999; cuid548; 182843 (Box 19)
  - DVD-R, 182755
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond A/P/A Panel, cuid549; 182844 (Box 19)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond A/P/A Panel, cuid550; 182845 (Box 19)
  - Cassettes, 182848
    - ACEH Indonesia, 1998 December 12; cuid551; 182850 (Box 19)
    - ACEH Indonesia, 1998 December 12; cuid552; 182851 (Box 19)
    - ACEH Indonesia, 1998 December 12; cuid553; 182852 (Box 19)
    - ACEH Indonesia, 1998 December 12; cuid554; 182853 (Box 19)
    - Albert Chong Works in Progress, cuid555; 182854 (Box 19)
    - Ancestors in the Americas Film Screening and Discussion, cuid556; 182855 (Box 19)
    - APA Studies Conference, 2004 April 16; cuid557; 182856 (Box 19)
    - APA Studies Conference, 2004 April 16; cuid558; 182857 (Box 19)
    - APA Studies Conference, 2004 April 16; cuid559; 182858 (Box 19)
    - Artists and History Making, cuid560; 182859 (Box 19)
    - The Atlantic World, 1997 October 11; cuid561; 182860 (Box 19)
    - Awards Ceremony, cuid562; 182861 (Box 19)
    - Backstage Pass Session III of Hidden Histories of Popular Music, cuid563; 182862 (Box 19)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid564; 182863 (Box 19)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid565; 182864 (Box 19)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid566; 182865 (Box 19)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid567; 182866 (Box 19)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid568; 182867 (Box 19)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid569; 182868 (Box 19)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid570; 182869 (Box 19)
    - Community Activism, cuid571; 182870 (Box 19)
    - Community Activism, cuid572; 182871 (Box 19)
    - Concrete Cultures Session I of Asian American Urban Practices, cuid573; 182872 (Box 19)
    - David Henry Hwang 20 Year Retrospective, 2000 November 14; cuid574; 182873 (Box 19)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid575; 182874 (Box 19)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid576; 182875 (Box 19)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid577; 182876 (Box 19)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid578; 182877 (Box 19)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid579; 182878 (Box 19)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid580; 182879 (Box 19)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid581; 182880 (Box 19)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid582; 182881 (Box 19)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid583; 182882 (Box 19)
    - Diaspora U.S., cuid584; 182883 (Box 19)
    - Diaspora U.S., cuid585; 182884 (Box 19)
    - Diaspora U.S., cuid586; 182885 (Box 19)
    - Diaspora U.S., cuid587; 182886 (Box 19)
    - Digital Dialogues: Asian-American Technoculture Practices, cuid588; 182887 (Box 19)
    - Freezone- Opening Remarks and Youth Cultures, 2000; cuid589; 182888 (Box 19)
    - Freezone--Youth Cultures, 2000; cuid590; 182889 (Box 19)
    - Freezone--Open Mic, 2000; cuid591; 182890 (Box 19)
    - Freezone--Representation/Presentation, 2000; cuid592; 182891 (Box 19)
    - Freezone--Situation Resolution and Creating Safe Spaces, 2000; cuid593; 182892 (Box 19)
    - Freezone--Addressing the Needs of Youth, 2000; cuid594; 182893 (Box 19)
    - Freezone--Youth Organizing, 2000; cuid595; 182894 (Box 19)
    - Freezone--Asian Youth Culture, 2000; cuid596; 182895 (Box 19)
    - Freezone--Panel, 2000; cuid597; 182896 (Box 19)
    - Freezone--Current Issues, 2000; cuid598; 182897 (Box 19)
    - Freezone--Community Involvement, 2000; cuid599; 182898 (Box 19)
    - Freezone--Expressive Cultures, 2000; cuid600; 182899 (Box 19)
    - Freezone--Closing Symposium Reflections and Conclusions, 2000; cuid601; 182900 (Box 19)
    - Fictions of Asian America, 2004 April 17; cuid602; 182901 (Box 19)
    - Fictions of Asian America, 2004 April 17; cuid603; 182902 (Box 19)
    - Fictions of Asian America, 2004 April 17; cuid604; 182903 (Box 19)
    - Fluid Cultures, cuid605; 182904 (Box 19)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel, cuid606; 182905 (Box 19)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel, cuid607; 182906 (Box 19)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel, cuid608; 182907 (Box 19)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel, cuid609; 182908 (Box 19)
    - Gender and Politics, cuid610; 182909 (Box 19)
    - Getting the Story Told, cuid611; 182910 (Box 19)
    - The Good Life Session I of Politics of Consumption, Pleasure, and Desire, cuid612; 182911 (Box 19)
    - History, Memory, Community, cuid613; 182912 (Box 19)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination, 2002 April 13; cuid614; 182913 (Box 19)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination, 2002 April 13; cuid615; 182914 (Box 19)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination, 2002 April 13; cuid616; 182915 (Box 19)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination, 2002 April 13; cuid617; 182916 (Box 19)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination, 2002 April 13; cuid618; 182917 (Box 19)
    - The John Huang Affair and Political Participation, cuid619; 182918 (Box 19)
    - Making History: New Settlements in the Americas, cuid620; 182919 (Box 19)
    - Magdalen Hsu-Li: Evolution National Tour, 1999; cuid621; 182920 (Box 19)
    - New Media and Community Building Roundtable, cuid622; 182921 (Box 19)
    - New Media and Community Building Roundtable, cuid623; 182922 (Box 19)
    - New Research/New Interpretation, cuid624; 182923 (Box 19)
    - Notes from the Asian Underground, cuid625; 182924 (Box 19)
    - Pan in Focus/Despers USA, cuid626; 184300 (Box 19)
    - Paradigm 2, The Americas, cuid627; 182925 (Box 19)
    - Program, 1998 November 13; cuid628; 182926 (Box 19)
    - The Real Deal? Asian American Cultural Politics, cuid629; 182927 (Box 19)
    - Reclaiming the Self/Reclaiming the History, cuid630; 182928 (Box 19)
    - Recovering Lives/Communities, cuid631; 182929 (Box 19)
    - Relocating: Enclaves Past, Present, and Future, cuid632; 182930 (Box 19)
    - Resident Aliens Session III of Cultural Citizenship and Pop Culture, cuid633; 182931 (Box 19)
    - Resources for Family History Preservation Workshop, cuid634; 182932 (Box 19)
    - Tape 1, cuid635; 182933 (Box 19)
    - To Wong Foo--The Migration of Popular Culture, cuid636; 182934 (Box 19)
    - Touring Chinatown--Problems and Possibilities, cuid637; 182935 (Box 19)
    - Touring Chinatown--Problems and Possibilities, cuid638; 182936 (Box 19)
    - Trinh Minh Ha Lecture, 2001 March 21; cuid639; 182937 (Box 19)
    - Vijay Iyer, 2000 February 23; cuid640; 182938 (Box 19)
    - Vijay Iyer Discussion, 2000 February 23; cuid641; 182939 (Box 19)
    - Where is Home for Asian-American Writers, cuid642; 182940 (Box 19)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond Teach In, cuid643; 182941 (Box 19)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond Teach In, cuid644; 182942 (Box 19)
    - Winifred Chin Paper Son Talk, 2003 April 14; cuid645; 182943 (Box 19)
- Series VII: Artifacts, 222137
  Series VII contains a large A/P/A banner.
  - Banner, Undated; 222138 (Box 21)
- Series VIII: 2016 Accretion
  This accretion consists of materials created and collected by A/P/A, including photo albums, flyers and other ephemera for A/P/A events, and audiovisual recordings on a variety of formats documenting A/P/A events and the work of artist-in-residence Fay Chiang.
  Arrangement
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  - Conferences, 1995-2002 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - Calendar of Events, 2010-2014 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Course Listing, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Event Ephemera, 1997-2015 (Box 22, Folder 6-14)
  - Defining "Communities of Interest", 2000 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Asian Pacific American Youth Alliance, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - US Census, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Legal Advice from Teach-in, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Photo Albums and Guest Book, circa 1995-2015 (Box 22)
  - Audiovisual Recordings of A/P/A Events, 2002-2004 (Box 23, Box 24)
  - Audiovisual Recordings of Artist-in-Residence Fay Chiang, circa 2002-2004 (Box 24)
- Series IX: 2017 Accretion
  This accretion to the records contains event material from 1997 to 2015. The event material consists of planning agendas, guest lists, promotional brochures and flyers, syllabi, receipts and correspondence. The events varied from symposiums and conferences to movie screenings and gallery openings with event topics that promoted a dialogue about the Asian American and Pacific American experience.
  - Overcoming Stigma in Asian American Mental Health, 2004 -10-01, 2004-10-02 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - South Asian Underground Film Fest, 2007-03-20, 2007-04-22 (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
  - Fall 2010 (Box 25, Folder 5-6)
  - Spring 2008 (Box 25, Folder 7-12)
  - A/P/A Courses, Undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Promotional Material, 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 14-17)
  - Spring 2007 (Box 25, Folder 18-22)
  - Spring 2007 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - Palates of Pleasure, 2001-03-19, 2001-03-21 (Box 26, Folder 3-5)
  - Spring 2011 (Box 26, Folder 6-8)
  - Fall 2009-Spring 2010, 2009-2010 (Box 26, Folder 9-13)